{
    "id": "cb472e4e0baf4d00b083095ce3920141",
    "title": "Make, take or leave: grammar exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "297f9f5d59bb4e1687dfc0633e2f928b",
            "title": "Make, Take Or Leave",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Can I ………………… a suggestion?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "leave",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "One must not …………………… more than one gives.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "leave",
                        "make",
                        "take"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Please …………………… a look at this.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "make",
                        "leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Can I ……………………… a message?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "leave",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I can’t …………………… an exception in your case.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "make",
                        "take",
                        "leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "My brother likes to ………………….. photos.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "leave",
                        "make"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have …………………. all arrangements for the party.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "taken",
                        "left",
                        "made"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She is old enough to ………………… her own bed now.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "make",
                        "leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "If you are tired why don’t you ………………….. a rest?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "take",
                        "make",
                        "leave"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She …………………… a deep breath.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "took",
                        "made",
                        "left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}